This is Chen Zhou's wife Su Mingyao
Yeah
And the Mrs Fu acknowledged by the Fu family
Mingyao, right
First time at the Fu residence
Make yourself at home
Thank you, Second Master Fu
It seems the wife Chen Zhou married
has quite impeccable manners
First time meeting the elders
Basic manners are naturally expected
Welcome home, Chen Zhou
Thank you. Mrs Fu, an honor to meet you
You are too polite, Mr Fu
Nancheng has been quite lively lately
Everyone says Mrs Fu has great taste
I am indeed curious
With so many people at the wedding
why did Mrs Fu choose Chen Zhou of all people
Because he was standing right there
I needed someone willing
to respect my choices
And he just happened to be the one